open cupboard
pick up tupperware
open tupperware
pick up stone
place down stone
pick up tupperware
close lid
pick up another tupperware
place in sink
turn on tap
pick up stone
place stone
adjust tap
test water
turn off tap
pick up tupperware
walk with tupperware
place down tupperware
Play music
Open door
Remove clothes
Remove clothes into machine
Put clothes in machine
Open up hamper
Put sock in hamper
Pick up backpack
Remove clothes from backpack
Remove carrier bag
Remove bag
Empty bag
Put clothes in washer
Adjust clothes in washer
Remove backpack
Pickup phone
Close app
Turn off washer
Adjust dial
Adjust settings
Close door
Turn on washer
Close app
Scoop washing powder
Open drawer
look at washing powder
look at drawer
put back washing powder
close drawer
[END SUBTITLE]